

BIOGRAPHY

I'm a 23 year old freelancer in web design and online work snuggled into the small town of Springfield, Tennessee. I have experience in the food industry and in education as a tutor and student worker. I love to travel, especially to the Eastern parts of Asia. My hobby is taking photos of my adventures and writing tips on my blog for other travelers.

f /thudangphat

/thu-dang-241a04b0

EXPERIENCE

FREELANCE

Self-Employed | May 2017 -

Designing websites as a subcontractor while using various e-commercial tools and applications.

STUDENT WORKER

UT Chattanooga | Sept 2015 - June 2016

Researched study abroad methods, managed TerraDotta system, organized student files, and performed as a ISEP Ambassador.

SERVER & TRAINER

Sekisui | Sept 2013 - Nov 2016

Trained new employees to ensure proper regulations of food distribution and customer service is above satisfaction.

EDUCATION

BACHELORS'S DEGREE: International Relations

UT Chattanooga | Aug 2012 - August 2017

Completed courses in cultural anthropology, international politics, public relations, and Vietnamese culture and religion.

BACHELOR'S DEGREE: Computer Science

UT Chattanooga | Aug 2012 - August 2017

Completed courses in computer forensics, Java programming, business administration, and software systems and development.

STUDY ABROAD

Chukyo University | Sept 2014 - Aug 2015

Completed courses in peace and argument, comparative culture, and Japanese management, language, and economics.

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Born in Vietnam and moved to the US at the age of one. Learned Vietnamese at home and Japanese in college and traveling.





JAPANESE 50%



REFERENCES

Kristin Labs | Field Director, at Institute for Study Abroad +802 275 8968 | kristinlabs@gmail.com

Yu Liang | Associate Professor at UT Chattanooga +423 425 4351 | yu-liang@utc.edu

SKILLS

Java

CSS/HTML

TerraDotta

Wordpress

Python